那是什麼？
What was that?
水龍頭
A faucet.
水滴不停
It wouldn't shut up.
- 你昨晚有睡著嗎？  - 沒有
-Did you sleep last night?  -No.
我會打給南茜  叫她找水電工來
I'll call Nancy and tell her to call a plumber.
絕對謹慎
Absolute discretion.
- 你能做到嗎？  - 向來可以
-Can I count on that?  -Always.
瑞蒙塔斯克
Raymond Tusk.
總統點名要他接任新副總統
The President wants to tap him  as the new VP.
- 你我不能讓那成真  - 為什麼？
-You and I cannot let that happen.  -Why not?
因為他有三分之一的財產  跟核能密不可分
Because a third of his fortune  is tied up in nuclear energy.
善可工業不希望  支持核能的商人進入白宮
SanCorp does not want a pro-nuclear  businessman in the White House.
反正市場正轉向天然氣
Market is shifting  toward natural gas anyway.
但塔斯克想拖住或是扭轉情勢
But Tusk wants to stall that shift  or reverse it.
副總統沒有那種影響力
Vice President doesn't have  that kind of influence.
這傢伙有  他和沃克關係非常好
This one would.  He and Walker are very close.
看著善可工業
And it's in neither of our best interests
市場地位縮減  對我們都不利
to see SanCorp's position  in the marketplace diminished.
- 該怎麼做？  - 只要塔斯克認為
-What's the ask?  -Tusk won't accept the nomination
股份有風險  就不會接受任命
if he thinks his holdings are at risk.
善可工業必須發起惡意接管
SanCorp needs to initiate a hostile takeover.
他的資產值三個善可工業
He's worth three times what SanCorp is.
我說的是子公司
I'm talking about the subsidiaries.
我們找那些精煉  和運輸鈾的公司
We go after the companies  that refine and ship the uranium,
- 輔助系統…  - 拜託，法蘭
-the support system that...  -Come on, Frank.
必須考量到股東  巨大的財務風險
There's stockholders to take into account,  huge financial exposure.
我們只要讓他分心
We just need to distract him.
使出一些象徵性手段  暗示一切還沒完
Send a few token salvos  and intimate there's more to come.
我只要你跟你的客戶提一下
All I'm asking is that you speak to your client
看看他們是否願意考慮這件事
and see if this is something  they might be willing to consider.
總統週五會宣佈塔斯克的事  我們時間不多
The President announces Tusk on Friday,  so we don't have a lot of time.
- 我會打幾通電話  - 謝了，瑞米
-I'll make some calls.  -Thank you, Remy.
如果他沒成功  我就得孤軍奮鬥
If he doesn't deliver,  I'm an invader without an army.
如果他成功  我就有反擊的機會
If he does, I've got a fighting chance.
我只是覺得  我們無法再繼續共事
I just didn't feel that we could work  together constructively any longer.
那是完全合法的理由…
I think that's a perfectly legitimate reason...
當然是的
Of course it is.
但你不能以懷孕為由開除她
But what you can't do is  fire someone for being pregnant.
她那麼說？
Is that what she's saying?
柯爾小姐聲稱你說過
Ms. Cole claims that you said,
我需要員工，不要母親
quote, I need employees, not mothers,
還有去專心懷寶寶吧
and, quote, go focus on your baby.
我可以看嗎？
Can I see that?
這完全是假的，我…
It's completely false. I...
- 我沒說過那種話  - 她說你有
-I never said that.  -She claims you did.
那是她的說法吧？
It's her word against mine, right?
陪審團特別同情孕婦
Well, juries are very sympathetic  with expecting mothers.
這是敲詐
This is extortion.
我們不想上法庭，克萊兒
We don't want this going to trial, Claire.
你和你老公都是公眾人物  這會引起極負面的報導
You and your husband are public figures.  This will result in some very bad press.
我建議我們回去跟他們和解
I suggest we go back to them  with a settlement offer.
- 我們需要逮捕紀錄  - 沒有
-We need the arrest record.  -There isn't any.
- 他們放他走  - 那就要知道是誰放的
-They let him go.  -Then we need to know who got him off.
如果安德沃涉入
If Underwood was involved,
就是濫用職權和腐敗
we are talking abuse of powers  and corruption.
我查過了，沒有檔案  沒有照相，什麼都沒有
I checked.  There's no files, no mug shot, nothing.
那就找出攔他車的警察
Then we need to find the cop  who pulled him over,
或是看到他進警局的人
or somebody who saw him  come into the station.
但是華府的警察？
But D.C. cops?
他們彼此照應  我們得小心點
They look after each other.  We need to be careful.
你在警局有熟人嗎？
Do you have any sources on the force?
像這樣的事  我沒有信得過的人
Not that I would trust  with something like this.
盧卡斯最初是做犯罪版的
You know, Lucas started out  on the crime beat.
我去問他有沒有熟人
I can see if he knows anyone.
- 他會幫我們嗎？  - 不知道
-Would he help us?  -I don't know.
- 也許吧  - 幫對手的忙？
-Maybe.  -Help out a competitor?
我們一直有連絡
We stayed in touch.
你肯定在說笑
You've gotta be kidding me.
這城市也太亂倫了吧
This town is way too incestuous.
我知道要求很過分
I know it's a lot to ask.
我還在努力想清楚緋聞，喬伊
I'm still trying to wrap my head  around the affair, Zoe.
如果你能給我連絡人  也許再為我擔保…
If you could just give me a contact  and maybe vouch for me...
你到現在才說  是因為你認為
Did you wait to bring this up until now  because you thought
我會難以拒絕？
it'd be harder for me to say no?
- 什麼意思？  - 在我們上床後…
-What do you mean?  -ln bed, right after we...
你不會真的以為  我會做那種事…
You don't actually think  I would do something like...
看來就是如此
It sure seems that way.
這麼說很嚴重，盧卡斯
This is huge, Lucas.
我努力避免搞砸我們的關係
I'm trying to avoid fucking up what we have.
不管是什麼關係  你在為難我
Whatever that is.  And you're making it really hard for me.
我不知道  我會是那種容易打發的人
I don't know that I'll ever be  the kind of person that makes it easy.
我不是在打發你  但不必讓我想起他吧
I'm not looking for easy.  But I don't need to be reminded of him.
- 我不能抹滅過去  - 我知道你不能
-I can't erase what I did.  -I know you can't.
但這真的很卑鄙
But this is really fucking manipulative.
那晚你說的是真心話嗎？
Did you mean  what you said the other night?
就是你可能…
That you probably...
聽到那些話時，我不知所措
I don't know what to do  when I hear something like that.
所以你載我去機場時  我才會如此沉默
That's why I was so quiet  when you drove me to the airport.
我當時生氣
I was angry.
脫口而出的
I just blurted it out.
真希望我沒說  至少不要像那樣
I wish I hadn't. At least not like that.
我不是因為你說了那些話  才利用你的
I'm not trying to take advantage of you  because you did.
- 他什麼也沒說  - 你也沒提？
-He hasn't said a word.  -And you haven't brought it up?
我只問他  是否還在考慮塔斯克
I just asked him if he was  still considering Tusk.
他說是的  但他想先跟你談，就這樣
He said yes, but that he wanted  to speak to you first. That's it.
真希望我們已經知道  他們是否談過了
I wish we knew if they'd spoken at all.
他有私人專線  我沒辦法追查
Well, he has his private line.  I can't track those calls.
- 法蘭  - 總統先生
-Frank.  -Mr. President.
告訴我聖路易的情況
Tell me about St. Louis.
他很難看得出來
He's a hard man to read.
我盡力試探
I did my best to probe him,
但還是沒探出他的傾向
but I don't think I left any wiser  to which way he's leaning.
儘管如此，我還是得說  他是超乎理想的最佳候選人
I must say, though, I think he is  by far and away the best candidate.
為何那麼說？
Why do you say that?
提名你最瞭解的人  不是很合理嗎？
Doesn't it make sense for you to  nominate someone you know so well?
我不瞭解他  所以才派你去聖路易
I don't know him.  That's why I sent you to St. Louis.
抱歉，總統先生  我不是那意思
Forgive me, Mr. President.  I didn't mean it that way.
我意思是全世界都熟知他
I meant that the world knows so well.
你、我  所有人都熟知瑞蒙塔斯克
You, me, everyone knows Raymond Tusk.
不必說服任何人他的價值
We don't need to convince anyone  of his worthiness.
但你說他還很猶豫？
But you said he still seems ambivalent?
所以我認為你該安排私人約談
Which is why I think you should  make a personal overture.
邀他到白宮
Invite him to the White House.
- 我不想表現急迫  - 我同意法蘭
-Well, I don't want to appear desperate.  -I agree with Frank.
邀他來是個很好的主意
Inviting him is a very good idea.
如果你認真考慮塔斯克  就該請他吃飯
If you're serious about Tusk,  you should wine and dine him.
讓他覺得自己很特別
Make him feel very special.
我相信我們能挪出時間
I'm sure we can find time in the schedule.
- 讓他多考慮幾天  - 時間剩不到一周了
-Let's give him a few more days.  -We have less than a week, sir.
不能拖過週五
I wouldn't wait any later than Friday.
週五有空檔，先生
We can make Friday work, sir.
好吧，看他是否有空
All right. Well, see if he's available.
你在做什麼？
What are you doing?
- 給我你的手機  - 為何？
-Give me your phone.  -Why?
給我就對了
Just give it to me.
你有發現異狀嗎？
Have you noticed anything weird in here?
東西被移動？失竊？
Stuff moved around?  Anything missing?
- 沒有  - 有人跟蹤你嗎？
-No.  -Anyone following you?
你發現什麼了？
What did you find out?
事情很嚴重，喬伊
This is serious, Zoe.
一路往上牽涉到局長
It goes way up,  as high as the Commissioner.
我必需求我在警隊的連絡人  才能拿到這個
I had to beg my contact  at Metro to give me this.
沒有魯索的攔車紀錄
No record of Russo getting pulled over,
但他記得當時魯索  跟一名妓女一起被帶進來
but he remembers there was  a call girl brought in with Russo.
那是她之前  被逮的其中一個紀錄
That's a file on one of her previous arrests.
我以前調查過警察包庇的案件
I've investigated police cover-ups before.
結果收到死亡威脅整整一年
I got death threats for a year.
你願意冒那風險？
Are you willing to take that risk?
是的
Yeah.
多久？
How long?
下次董事會是三周後
The next board of directors  meeting is three weeks from now.
太遲了，瑞米，聽著
That is too late. Remy, look,
總統在一周內就會提名塔斯克
the President is gonna  nominate Tusk in a week or less.
我要求史考特康尼漢  召開特別會議了
I've urged Scott Cunningham  to call a special meeting,
但不會一夕之間辦成
but that doesn't happen overnight.
這種事會引起全體反彈
There's a lot of machinery  in a corporate attack like this.
我要親自見史考特康尼漢
I want to meet Scott Cunningham myself.
我不跟你和史考特會面  你懂規矩
I'm not sitting you down with Scott.  You know the rules.
情況特殊
These are extraordinary circumstances.
法蘭，善可工業的高層  不見政客，就這樣
Frank, SanCorp's officers  do not meet with politicians, period.
你要透過我  跟史考特康尼漢談
You talk to me, I talk to Scott Cunningham,
或是反過來，那是規矩
and vice versa. That's how it works.
好吧，瑞米，就依你的
All right, Remy.  Whatever you think best.
- 有消息再通知你  - 南茜！
-I'll call you when I know more.  -Nancy!
所有我保持高度尊重的事情中  規矩不在其一
Of all the things I hold in high regard,  rules are not one of them.
若能直接找源頭  我不會把命運
I will not place my fate solely  in the hands of a middleman
完全托付給中間人
if I can go directly to the supplier.
訂一張明早到亞特蘭大的機票  通知米契
Book a flight to Atlanta.  Tomorrow morning. Let Meechum know.
好的，議員
Yes, sir.
她在維吉尼亞州林奇堡長大  就讀過洛利默高中
She grew up in Lynchburg, Virginia,  went to Lorimer High School
直到高二那年輟學
until she dropped out sophomore year,
之後就沒有公共紀錄
and then after that, there's no public record.
但這裏只記錄她在2012年4月
But all it says here is that she was fined $300
當街拉客被罰三百元
for loitering on April, 2012.
有人得去一趟林奇堡
One of us has to go to Lynchburg.
- 找父母、同學、老師  - 我去
-Parents, classmates, teachers.  -I'll do it.
那你和我得打電話召妓
Okay. Well then, you and l  have to call escort services.
我樂意幫忙  但不想打12小時的電話
I'm willing to lend a hand, but not  by making cold calls 12 hours a day
跟妓女閒扯淡
just to get hung up on by hookers.
她在哪裏被逮？
Where was she arrested?
- 康乃狄克街  - 2460號
-Connecticut Ave.  -2460.
那是地方大飯店的住址
That's the address  of the District Grand Hotel.
善可工業
我不喜歡不速之客，法蘭
I'm not a fan of surprise visits, Frank.
瑞米不安排會面
Remy wouldn't arrange a meeting.
有瑞米丹頓的存在  我們才不必見面
Remy Danton exists  so we don't have to meet.
我必須跟你談
I needed to speak with you.
國會旅行報告裏
There's a congressional travel report
會記載你的亞特蘭大之旅
that puts you on a trip to Atlanta
正好跟我中途離開  投資者簡報同一天
the same day I was pulled out  of an investors' briefing.
那類的巧合是我們想避免的
Those are the sort of coincidences  we want to avoid.
你在跟投資者報告  瑞蒙塔斯克嗎？
Were you briefing your investors  on Raymond Tusk?
米契是自己人
Meechum can be trusted.
我為何要跟他們提塔斯克？
Why would I be speaking  to them about Tusk?
- 我以為瑞米告訴你了  - 沒有
-I thought Remy filled you in.  -No.
他完全沒說  提名副總統的事嗎？
He didn't say anything about  the Vice Presidential nomination?
沒有，我寧願不知道
He didn't. And I have a feeling  I'd rather not be told.
相信我，你會想知道
Trust me, you want to know.
我以前面對過陪審團，法蘭
I've appeared in front of  grand juries before, Frank.
說實話會比較簡單
It's much easier when you can tell the truth.
拜託，別害我不得不說謊
Please, don't put me in  a position where I have to lie.
如果塔斯克有總統當靠山
If Tusk has the President's ear,
你會看到這個總統府
you will see this administration  shift its support
轉向支持核能  不支持天然氣
toward nuclear energy  and away from natural gas.
去找他的子公司和供應商
His subsidiaries and his suppliers.  Go after them.
法蘭，談話到此為止
Frank, we should end  this conversation right now.
只要他覺得資產有風險
He will not accept  the nomination if his assets
且無法對抗威脅時  他就不會接受任命
are in a blind trust  and he can't fight off the threat.
- 好了  - 史考特…
-Okay, we're done.  -Scott...
我不想再聽了
I don't wanna hear another word.
回機場吧
Go back to the airport.
想個你今天  必須來亞特蘭大的好理由
Figure out a good reason  you needed to be in Atlanta today.
在下個街角停車  我會叫我的車來接我
You can pull over at the next corner.  I'll have my car pick me up.
- 最後一杯嗎？  - 再來一杯
-One last one?  -Another.
- 要喝什麼嗎？  - 白酒
-Can I get you something?  -White wine.
記在我帳上
Put that on my tab.
- 謝謝你  - 我的榮幸
-Thank you.  -My pleasure.
快要點最後一次酒了
They're about to call last call.
沒關係，我不太能喝
That's all right.  I don't have much of a tolerance.
- 再來一杯？  - 不用了
-One more?  -No. I'm good.
你好
Hey.
你該上樓的
You should head upstairs.
我在等你
I was waiting for you.
- 那是新水龍頭嗎？  - 是的
-ls that the new faucet?  -Yeah.
如何？
How'd it go?
不好，瑞米圖謀不軌
Not good. Remy's up to something.
他不回我電話
He's not returning my phone calls.
我能怎麼做？
What can I do?
告訴我你做了什麼夢
Tell me what you were dreaming.
很糟的夢，法蘭斯
Oh, it was so awful, Francis.
他也不讓我睡
He's not letting me sleep either.
不是他，是孩子們
Yeah. It's not him. It's the kids.
我跟孩子們在後院玩
I was playing with them in the backyard,
女孩爬到藤蔓上面去
and the girl was climbing on the vines,
我一直叫她下來，然而…
and I kept telling her  to stop and get down, and...
藤蔓把她纏住，不肯放手
The vines just took hold of her,  and they wouldn't let go.
她大聲尖叫
And she was screaming so loud,
我不斷地用力拉
and I just kept pulling harder and harder,
最後她被撕成兩半
and she just ripped in half.
過來，好了
Come here. Come here. Okay.
老天！
Jesus!
你到清晨2點才回我電話？
You wait until after 2:00  in the morning to return my call?
想進入語音信箱嗎？
You trying to get my voicemail?
我們要說的話  不能在手機上說
The conversations we're having  we can't be having on cell phones.
你在哪裏？
Where are you?
克萊兒在樓上睡覺
Claire is sleeping upstairs.
你不該去見康尼漢
You shouldn't have gone  to see Cunningham.
他說你沒提塔斯克
He says you didn't bring up Tusk.
你真以為他會承認？
You really think he'd admit to that?
這麼做是內線交易
Ifwe go through with this,  it's insider trading.
在我看來  他不像第二次聽到這消息
He didn't strike me as a man  hearing the news for the second time.
你以為我在耍花招
You want to believe I'm playing games,
我能撒手不管
I can walk away from the whole thing.
但此刻你只有我
But I'm all you've got right now.
我在幫你和善可工業  不是你們在幫我
I'm the one doing you and SanCorp a favor,  not the other way around.
我看得出來我被利用，法蘭  我只想知道為什麼
I can tell when I'm being used, Frank.  I just want to know what for.
我不會利用事後甩不掉的人
I don't use people unless  I can throw them away afterwards.
我在試著強化我們的合作關係
I'm trying to strengthen our partnership.
聽來簡直一派胡言
Smells an awful lot like bullshit.
別擺架子
Don't condescend.
為你工作八年了
Eight years I worked on your staff.
從沒踏進過你的大門
And never once made it further  than your front doorstep.
現在我在你客廳，法蘭
Well, now I'm in your living room, Frank.
不是因為你教的
It's not because of what you taught me.
是因為我終於認清自己的價值
It's because I finally woke up  to what my value is,
還有以前多沒價值  替你賣命
and how undervalued I was,  slaving away for you.
這是生意  把自怨自艾的故事留給自己
This is business.  Keep your sob story to yourself.
我想維持
I want to maintain the influence
我在白宮辛苦經營的影響力
that I have worked to achieve  in the White House,
那也是你在白宮的影響力
which translates into the influence  that you have in the White House,
透過我
through me.
我明天會再連絡史考特
I'll get in touch with Scott again tomorrow.
看看是否能加速進行
See if we can push this forward faster.
謝了，瑞米
Thank you, Remy.
但你得讓我用自己的方式
But you gotta let me do this my way.
她說得很清楚
The message was very clear.
她不想和解，不管金額多少
She doesn't want a settlement,  no matter what the figure.
就算把世安還她？
Even if we give her WorldWell back?
她想上法庭
She wants to go to court.
他們說下周就會收到正式傳票
They said we can expect  a formal summons next week.
- 太荒唐了  - 她的律師同意
-This is ludicrous.  -Her lawyers agree.
他們也寧願和解  但她不配合
They'd much prefer a settlement, too,  but she's not playing ball.
我會繼續催他們  但在此同時
I'll keep pushing them.  But in the meantime,
你該開始整理  你跟她的所有通訊往來
you should start gathering all the  correspondence you ever had with her.
電郵、筆記，所有文件
Emails, notes, every scrap of paper.
好，謝謝，奧利弗
Okay. Thanks, Oliver.
我只想找到她
All I'm trying to do is find her.
我有2012年4月的逮捕紀錄
I've got an arrest record from April, 2012,
還知道她在一月時  坐客戶的車被警察攔下
and I know she was pulled over  with a client in January.
那女孩很有潛力
That girl. She had so much potential.
她為何輟學？
Why did she drop out?
如我說的，這樣是違反道德的
Like I said, it's an ethical breach for me
我不能討論有關…
to discuss anything that has to do...
我跟她父母談過了
I spoke to her parents.
他父親非常暴力
Her father was very combative.
是家裏問題嗎？
Was there trouble at home?
父親是不是…
The father. Did he...
我不會談瑞秋的事
I won't speak about Rachel.
可以跟我說你一般的工作
Can you talk to me about your job in general,
大概處理哪一類的案子？
the sorts of cases you deal with  in an abstract way?
當我關心某個學生
When I'm concerned about a student,
尤其是可能牽涉到犯罪活動時
especially if there's possible  criminal activity involved,
我的責任是連絡地方檢察官
it's my duty to contact the DA's Office.
如果檢察官提出告訴
Now, if the DA pursues charges,
學生就得作證  指控自己的父母
the student has to testify  against their own parent.
那對年輕人來說  是很難做的決定
That's a difficult decision  for a young person to make.
非常難
Extremely difficult.
逃跑反而比較容易
It could be easier to run away.
會議安排在明天  塔斯克7點半飛到
It's set for tomorrow.  Tusk lands at 7:30
再直接去白宮  和總統共進晚餐
and then heads straight to the White House  for dinner with the President.
- 這在官方行程上嗎？  - 沒有
-ls it on the official schedule?  -No.
- 必須有  - 我不能那麼做
-We need it to be.  -Well, I can't do that.
總統特別要我別寫上去
The President specifically asked  that I leave it off.
其實那反倒好  我們可以利用那點
Actually, that's good.  We can make that work.
你能安排柏許和總統會面嗎？
Can you set up a meeting  between Birch and the President?
關於什麼？
About what?
他可以提供副總統人選意見
So he can give him his 2 cents  about who he will nominate.
不該把柏許扯進來
I don't think we want Birch getting involved.
- 他絕不會有機會  - 你打算怎樣？
-He'll never get the chance.  -What are you planning?
你能安排今天稍晚會面嗎？  可不可以？
Can you set up a meeting  for later today? Yes or no?
我相信我能挪出時間
I'm sure I can squeeze it in.
很好，我會跟柏許說  打電話給他
Good. I'll talk to Birch.  Get him on the phone.
這跟塔斯克的晚宴一樣  不能寫上去
This has to stay off the books,  just like the dinner with Tusk.
- 好  - 還有最後
-Okay.  -And finally.
你有能開除的排程員嗎？
Do you have a scheduler that you can fire?
法蘭安德沃  看你的電郵
珍妮，我有消息要給你
Janine, I've got something for you.
這是什麼？
What is this?
總統現在到週五的秘密行程
The President's OTR schedule  between now and Friday.
- 你怎麼拿到的？  - 那不重要
-How'd you get this?  -lt doesn't matter.
看他今天下午跟誰會面
Look who he's meeting with this afternoon.
- 鮑伯柏許  - 再看週五晚
-Bob Birch.  -And look at Friday night.
瑞蒙塔斯克  這不算最不可思議的會面
Raymond Tusk. These aren't the  craziest meetings for him to be having.
那為何沒列在官方行程裏？
Then why aren't they  on the official schedule?
他在考慮提他們當副總統
He's considering them for Vice President.
那理由足以列入秘密行程
I'd say that's reason enough  to keep them secret.
立刻發佈出去
Get this out, right away.
議長先生  聽說你是副總統人選
Mr. Speaker, I'm hearing that you're gonna  be considered for the Vice Presidency.
《頭條報導》報導說  你此刻正要前往白宮
Slugline is reporting that you're  heading to the White House right now.
- 我…沒有  - 你不是去白宮？
-I'm... No.  -You're not headed to the White House?
對，總統只是要我提供意見
Yes. The President just wants my input.
但有可能你也被列入考慮
But there's the possibility that you  might be under consideration yourself.
我不清楚，抱歉
Not that I'm aware of. Excuse me.
- 行程怎麼流出去的？  - 有人洩漏，總統
-How did the schedule get out?  -lt got leaked, sir,
排程辦公室裏的人
by someone in the scheduling office.
- 蓄意嗎？  - 是意外
-On purpose?  -Accidentally.
電郵附錯了附件
A wrong attachment  to an email that went wide.
不管是誰，給我開除
Well, whoever it was, I want them out.
已經開除了
I already let them go.
- 柏許到了嗎？  - 他在外面等著
-ls Birch here yet?  -He's waiting outside.
取消，告訴他臨時有事
Well, cancel the meeting.  Tell him something came up.
- 我不想助長流言  - 好的，總統
-I don't want to feed the frenzy.  -Yes, sir.
幫我接私人專線
Give me the private line, please.
我家這條街有三輛衛星轉播車
There are three satellite trucks on my street.
我被困在自己家裏
I'm trapped in my own home.
排程辦公室裏有人出了錯
Somebody in the scheduling office  fucked up.
你真的考慮柏許？
Are you seriously considering Birch?
當然沒有
Absolutely not.
過程失控了，葛瑞
We are losing control of the process, Garrett.
我每次跟你說話  你從不回答
Every time I've spoken to you,  you've never spoken back.
雖然我們互看不順眼
Although given our mutual disdain,
我不怪你沉默以對
I can't blame you for the silent treatment.
也許我找錯聽眾了
Perhaps I'm speaking  to the wrong audience.
你聽得到嗎？
Can you hear me?
你到底有沒有語言能力  還是你只懂邪惡？
Are you even capable of language,  or do you only understand depravity?
彼得，是你嗎？
Peter, is that you?
別再躲在我腦裏，出來吧
Stop hiding in my thoughts and come out.
拿出你生前沒有的死亡勇氣
Have the courage in death  that you never had in life.
出來吧，看著我的眼睛  說你必須說的事
Come out, look me in the eye  and say what you need to say.
天堂或地獄都沒有慰藉
There is no solace above or below.
只有我們
Only us.
渺小、孤獨、奮鬥  不停地爭鬥
Small, solitary,  striving, battling one another.
我向自己祈禱、為自己祈禱
I pray to myself, for myself.
你好
Hello?
是誰？
Who is it?
我的律師說我不該跟你說話
My lawyer said I shouldn't be talking to you.
我的律師也是
Mine said the same thing.
我不會改變心意，克萊兒
I'm not gonna change my mind, Claire.
我犯了錯  我當時生氣，一時衝動
I made a mistake.  I got upset, and I acted impulsively.
我才是犯了錯的人  一開始不該和你合作
I was the one who made the mistake  by partnering with you in the first place.
好吧，那我們倆可以承認
Well, then, can we please both admit
事情不該如此  我們能找到和平的方法…
that it wasn't meant to be,  and we can find an amicable way...
- 不能  - 你要什麼？
-No, we can't.  -What do you want?
傳遞訊息
To send a message.
像你這樣的組織  拿九成的補助金
Organizations like yours  get 90% of the grant money,
再去滿足破壞環境的贊助商
then cozy up to corporate sponsors  who destroy the environment.
你所聲稱的全是謊言
The things you're claiming are lies.
我從沒提過你懷孕
I never mentioned your pregnancy.
我跟艾薇琳柏斯特連絡過
I got in touch with Evelyn Baxter.
記得她嗎？我們聊了很久
Remember her?  We had a long conversation.
看來你總是  砍掉跟你意見不合的人
It seems that you have a history of  axing people who disagree with you.
她會為我作證
She'll be testifying on my behalf.
你逼她開除的八個人也會
So will eight of the people  that you made her fire.
如果你要的是道歉  我就是來道歉的
Ifyou want an apology,  I'm here to offer you one,
提供你認為合理的補償
and to give you whatever you think is fair.
這案子會因為你老公的關係  引起全國的注意
This case is gonna get national attention  because of who you're married to.
我會有講台說出我想說的事
I'll have a platform to say what I want to say.
那價值遠超過  你能提供的任何補償
That's worth more  than anything you could offer.
聽著，我知道  我們有不同的人生觀
Listen, I know we have  different philosophies,
但努力達成的目標  是完全一樣的
but what we're trying to achieve  is exactly the same thing.
我們不該彼此敵對
We shouldn't be fighting each other.
感覺到了嗎？胎動？
Do you feel that? The kicking?
我不會讓你這種人  破壞我孩子要居住的世界
I won't let people like you fuck up  the world my child has to live in.
如果我得說謊才能做到
If I have to tell a few lies to do that,
至少我從你那裏學到一件  有價值的事
at least I learned  one valuable thing from you.
- 要喝什麼？  - 純格蘭利威
-What can I get for you?  -Glenlivet, neat.
訴訟嗎？
The lawsuit?
還有其他事
And other things.
什麼其他事？
What other things?
我沒辦法跟你保證
You know, I cannot guarantee you
一切都會成功
that all of this is gonna succeed.
不是那個
Oh, it's not that.
你告訴我，不然我繼續猜
You can tell me, or I can keep guessing.
你會翻白眼的
You'll roll your eyes.
對你不會
Not at you.
我在想當我們倆其中一人死時
I was thinking about when one of us dies.
不管是你或我
Whether it's you first or me...
如果是我，我相信會是我
Well, if it is me, and I'm sure it will be,
你不會孤獨太久
you won't be alone for long.
不，我是說我們會留下什麼？
No. I mean, what will we leave behind?
我們已經有了成就
We've accomplished a great deal.
我希望我們會有更多成就
And I intend for us to accomplish a lot more.
- 但為了誰呢？  - 為了彼此
-But for whom?  -For each other.
可是如果我們…
But if we're not...
我真蠢
I'm being silly.
你出過書嗎？
Have you ever been published?
很多次了
Many times.
真是個蠢問題
I guess that's a stupid question.
你不像窮苦潦倒的藝術家
You don't seem like a starving artist.
別以貌取人
Don't judge a book by its cover.
你的笑真美
You have a nice laugh.
是嗎？
Really?
很迷人
It's very attractive.
你住飯店嗎？
Are you staying at the hotel?
你想來我房間嗎？
You want to come up to my room?
那要看情況
That depends.
我要付多少錢？
Well, how much would that cost me?
那些似乎就對了
That seems about right.
閉上眼睛
Close your eyes.
把手伸出來
Put out your hands.
現在張開眼睛
Now open them up.
我在找這個女人
I'm trying to find this woman.
如果你逼我拿出警徽
If you make me pull out my badge,
我就得逮捕你
I have to take you in.
但我不想那麼做
But I don't want to do that.
別把事情鬧大
Let's not make a scene.
我以前常看到她
I used to see her around.
她離開這行了  我們很少連絡
She left the business, though.  We haven't really kept in touch.
知道她可能在哪嗎？
Any idea where she might be?
我有個朋友在喬治城的餐廳
A friend of mine saw her waiting tables
看到她在當服務生
at a restaurant in Georgetown.
我想問的問題是…
I guess the question I'm trying to ask is...
那一步值得嗎？
Is it even worth that step?
基本上對你這年紀的女人來說  非常困難
The bottom line is that for a woman  your age, it's extremely hard.
你曾流產過嗎？
Have you ever had a miscarriage?
沒有，我…
No. I...
我曾經很晚才來，但我…
I've been late before, but I don't...
我不是很確定
You know, I don't know.  I don't know exactly.
你墮過胎嗎？
Have you had any abortions?
三次
Three.
那就更難了
That can make it more difficult.
我不是在勸阻你
I'm not trying to dissuade you,
但請你在做決定前  務必深思熟慮
but please make sure you think  long and hard before you decide.
但有可能嗎？
But it's possible?
假設你和你老公都符合標準
Assuming you and your husband  fit all the criteria?
是的，有可能
Yes, it's possible.
好的
Okay.
什麼？那根本不是我的問題
What? Well, that's hardly my problem.
你去辦…
No, you get on it. It's...
我再回電，怎麼了？
I have to call you back. What is it?
善可工業的股票
SanCorp's stock.
過去四小時漲了百分之35
It's up 35% in the last four hours.
財經新聞都在報導
It's all over the financial news.
塔斯克出招了
Tusk is making a play.
給瑞米打電話
Get Remy on the phone.
安德沃議員在三線
Congressman Underwood on line three.
我正要打給你
I was just about to call you.
我今晚要在總統之前  見到塔斯克
I need to meet with Tusk before  he sees the President tonight.
- 他已經來了  - 在白宮嗎？
-He's already here.  -At the White House?
他決定提早幾小時到
He decided to come in a few hours early.
飛機半小時前降落了
His plane landed half an hour ago.
- 知道他在哪嗎？  - 不知道
-Do you know where he is?  -I don't know.
他自己的車去接他的  我剛才知道
He had his own car pick him up.  I just found out.
瑞米不在辦公室  我在辦公室和手機都留話了
Remy's not in his office.  I left word there and on his cell.
聽著，你一知道他在哪裏  就打給我
Look, you need to call me the moment  you know where he is.
好的
Okay.
現在只有午餐，希望沒問題
It's just the lunch menu right now.  I hope that's okay.
沒問題
Yeah. That's fine.
服務生馬上過來
Your server will be with you shortly.
瑞秋在嗎？
Is Rachel working?
不在，她週日才會來
No. I don't think  she's scheduled till Sunday.
今天下午是史蒂芬妮
Stephanie will be with you this afternoon.
謝謝
Thanks.
週日再來嗎？
Should we come back Sunday?
我馬上回來
I'll be right back.
抱歉，有什麼事嗎？
Excuse me.  Can I help you with something?
我在找化妝室
Yeah. I was just looking for the bathroom.
化妝室不在這邊  在你右邊直走到底
The bathroom is out this door,  to your right, down the hall.
- 那邊嗎？謝了  - 好
-That way? Thanks.  -Yeah.
除非你想用辦公室的廁所
Unless you want to use  the restroom in the office.
- 你打給誰？  - 瑞秋
-Who are you calling?  -Rachel.
瑞秋珀斯納嗎？
Rachel Posner?
我是喬伊邦斯  《頭條報導》的記者
My name is Zoe Barnes.  I'm a reporter at slugline.com.
我知道彼得魯索的事
I know about Peter Russo.
瑞秋？
Rachel?
若不想看到你和魯索的報導  我們就該見面
快點，瑞秋
Come on, Rachel.
你不該提到魯索
You shouldn't have mentioned Russo.
- 她會回的  - 換作是我就不回
-She'll write back.  -I wouldn't if I was her.
在哪裏？
你知道多少？
How much do you know?
他被攔車時，你和他在一起
That you were with him  when he was pulled over.
- 還有誰知道？  - 只有我
-Who else knows?  -Just me.
我能保密，但我要知道更多
I can keep it that way, but I need more.
- 就這麼多了  - 你說謊
-There is no more.  -You're lying.
沒錯，他被警察攔車時  我和他在一起
Yeah, I was with him  when he got pulled over.
他們帶走了他，放了我  不知他後來怎麼了
They took him away and let me go.  I don't know what happened to him.
他沒被起訴
He was never charged.
那麼你知道的比我多
You know more than me, then.
沒人來找過你吧？
No one ever came to talk to you?
- 找我做什麼？  - 要你保持沉默
-About what?  -To keep you quiet.
做那行的不接吻也不多話
You don't kiss and tell in that business.
- 就算是遇到議員嗎？  - 尤其是遇到議員
-Not even when it's a congressman?  -Especially when it's a congressman.
法蘭安德沃沒找過你？
Frank Underwood never approached you?
他是誰？
Who's that?
你太聰明了，故意裝傻，瑞秋
You're too smart to play dumb, Rachel.
你知道他是誰
You know who that is.
名字有點耳熟
Name rings a bell.
我不常看新聞
I try not to follow the news.
太多熟面孔
Too many familiar faces.
道格史坦普呢？
How about Douglas Stamper?
沒聽過
Never heard of him.
我知道的都告訴你了
I've told you everything I know.
我知道你父親做了什麼
I know about what your father did.
你不幫我，我就報導魯索
If you don't help me, I'll write about Russo.
我會寫你是妓女
I'll write that you were a prostitute,
還會寫你為何離家
and I'll write about why you left home.
就寫吧，婊子
Go to town, bitch.
所以呢？
So?
她提到你和你老闆
She mentioned both you and your boss.
- 什麼事？  - 她沒說
-What exactly?  -She didn't say.
她似乎只知道  他被攔車時，我在車裏
All she seemed to know was that I was  in the car with him when he got pulled over.
你沒承認別的事吧？
And you didn't admit to more than that?
沒有，我完全照你的意思說
No. I said everything  exactly like you told me to.
- 你真以為我會說出來？  - 冷靜
-You really think I'd spill my guts?  -Calm down.
你為何不告訴我他會自殘？  否則我絕不會做的
Why didn't you tell me he was gonna  hurt himself? I never would've done it.
我哪知道？
How could I have known?
- 真希望一切趕快結束  - 會的
-I just want all this to go away.  -lt will.
全都會的
All of it.
我保證
I promise.
要我幫你叫晚餐嗎？
Do you want me to order you dinner?
- 道格在哪裏？  - 不知道，他提早走了
-Where's Doug at?  -I don't know. He left early.
- 幫我打給他，好嗎？  - 好
-Call him for me, will you?  -Yes, sir.
再過13分鐘
Thirteen minutes from now,
塔斯克會和總統見面
Tusk will meet with the President,
除非他沒在那裏
if he isn't there already.
你從來不是盟友，對吧？
You've never been an ally, have you?
慢慢地往前推進
Pressing on with your slow,  incessant march.
就算我沒有  時間也會殺了魯索
Time would've killed Russo if I hadn't,
就像它有一天會殺了我
just as it will kill me someday.
殺了所有的人
Kill us all.
先生，我在道格的語音信箱  留言了
Sir, I just got Doug's voicemail.
不知他在哪裏
I wonder where he's at.
也許是他
Well, maybe this is him.
弗萊迪？
Freddy?
六月酒館
抱歉，法蘭，我得當牆頭草
Sorry, Frank. I had to trade up.
善可工業是大魚  但瑞蒙塔斯克是大鯨魚
SanCorp's a big fish,  but Raymond Tusk is a whale.
要吃什麼嗎，法蘭？
Can I get you something, Frank?
現在不用，謝了，弗萊迪
Nothing right now. Thank you, Freddy.
你們好好談吧
I'll leave y'all to it.
希望你不介意瑞米告訴我  你的這個小秘密
I hope you don't mind that Remy told me  about this little secret of yours.
我本來想找個  讓你舒服點的地方
I wanted a place  where you'd feel comfortable.
你不是應該在白宮嗎？
Shouldn't you be at the White House?
我怎能錯過華府最好的肋排？
How could I pass up the chance  to eat the best ribs in Washington?
瑞米告訴你善可工業的事了
Remy told you about SanCorp.
今天收盤時，我持股百分之3
As of closing bell today, I own 3%.
到下週末時  我會持股超過百分之10
By the end of next week, I'll own over 10%.
足以確認他們不會給我找麻煩
Enough to make sure  they can't cause me any trouble.
真是勇敢之舉，我很尊重
A valiant effort, though. I respect that.
那為何找我來？
So why are we here?
我告訴過你  我讓你仔細考慮到今天
I told you I'd give you  until today to think things over.
- 我是個遵守諾言的人  - 我還是沒興趣
-I'm a man who keeps my word.  -And I'm still not interested.
在聖路易時  你要我說得更具體點
You wanted me to be more  specific back in St. Louis.
那會是個好開始
That would be a good start.
英國在150年前  為何對中國發動戰爭？
Why did Britain go to war  with China 150 years ago?
我沒心情猜謎
I'm in no mood for riddles.
讓我幽默一下吧
Humor me a moment.
- 鴉片  - 比鴉片更重大，法蘭
-Opium.  -lt was bigger than opium, Frank.
那只是個藉口
That was simply the excuse.
北京想作主  不想受西方控制
Peking wanted to call the shots  instead of the West.
跟我們現在面臨的問題一樣
It's the same problem we're facing now.
但沒人喜歡貿易戰爭  更不用說軍事戰爭
But nobody wants a trade war,  much less a military one.
你的鴉片是什麼？
And what's your opium?
釤149，我的核反應堆需要
Samarium-149.  I need it for my reactors.
中國控制全世界  百分之95的供給量
China controls 95% of the world's supply.
你擔心我們的貨幣不平衡  我們的外債…
And you're worried about the imbalance  in our currency, our foreign debt...
- 全部都是  - 你已經有總統當靠山了
-All of it.  -You already have the President's ear.
關稅由國會控制
Trade tariffs are controlled by Congress.
你在那裏比葛瑞更有影響力
You have a lot more influence  there than Garrett does.
那也是最初  我要你留在那裏的原因
It's the reason I wanted you  to stay there in the first place.
你到底要我怎麼做？
And what exactly would you want me to do?
我還不確定
Well, that part I don't know yet.
必須等看看中國怎麼做
We'll have to wait and see  how things play out with Chinese.
我已經說過了  我不開空白支票
I've already told you  I will not do a blank check.
我得說我很驚訝，法蘭
I must say I'm surprised, Frank.
你有務實的好名聲
You have a reputation for pragmatism.
我也避免有簽賣身契的名聲
And I also have avoided  a reputation for indentured servitude.
我從不提議超過兩次，法蘭
I never make an offer more than twice, Frank.
現在就告訴我  你是否願意合作
Tell me now if I can  count on your cooperation.
你不是在提議合作  你是在要求監督
You're not offering cooperation,  you're demanding tutelage.
所以讓我跟你提議吧
So let me make you a proposal.
我絕對願意和你平等合作
I am absolutely willing  to work together as equals.
我會認真看待你的想法  就跟總統一樣
I will take your opinions seriously,  just as the President does.
但我不會事先做保證
But I will not  bind myself to them in advance.
如果你沒興趣，那就算了
If that doesn't interest you, fair enough.
祝你好運  能在接下來的四天內找到
Good luck finding a Vice President  in the next four days
跟我一樣務實的副總統
who will prove as pragmatic as l.
你買不到忠誠的，瑞蒙
You can't purchase loyalty, Raymond.
不是我心裏想的那種
Not the sort I have in mind.
如果你想贏得我的忠誠  那你得用你的忠誠回報
If you want to earn my loyalty,  then you have to offer yours in return.
只要我們能同意那點
And if we can agree to that.
那麼你是個有想像力的人
Well, you're a man with imagination.
等等
Wait.
如果史坦普本人在那裏
If Stamper was there himself,
這會比失蹤的逮捕檔案更嚴重
this goes much deeper than a lost arrest file.
我們來想想
Well, let's think about this.
魯索給他什麼？
What did Russo gain him?
在哈利遜堡的豪宅
A mansion in Harrisburg.
安德沃想要的比那個多
Underwood thinks bigger than that.
- 那怎樣？  - 不知道
-Then what?  -I don't know.
他控制賓州
He controls Pennsylvania.
他在白宮有影響力
He has influence in the White House.
沃克需要州重選…
Walker needs the state for re-election...
不可能只是沃克
No. No, it can't just be Walker.
總統提名國務卿時出賣了他
The President backstabbed him  for the Secretary of State nomination.
一定是別的原因
It has to be something else.
總統欠他的
The President would owe him.
欠什麼？
But what?
他們已經一周見一次了
They already meet once a week.
教育法案嗎？具體是什麼？
The Education Bill? I mean, what?  What specifically?
他可能想要當副總統
He could be after the VP nomination.
那不合理
That doesn't make sense, though.
副總統的空缺  是因為魯索失利了
The VP slot is on the table  because Russo tanked.
安德沃本來要他贏
Underwood wanted him to win.
除非他不想
Unless he didn't.
也許他要魯索自我毀滅
Maybe he wanted Russo to self-destruct.
迫使馬修競選
To force Matthews to run.
沒錯，等下周馬修勝利時…
Exactly. And then next week,  when Matthews wins...
總統欽點安德沃
The President taps Underwood.
總統先生
Mr. President.
塔斯克先生
Mr. Tusk.
謝謝你這麼短時間趕來
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
請坐，法蘭
Have a seat, Frank.
我有件事要坦白
I have a confession to make.
瑞蒙和我認識好幾年了
Raymond and l  have known each other for years.
我們沒有公開  但他一直是我信任的顧問
We don't publicize it,  but he's been a trusted advisor to me.
我派你去聖路易  他才能多多瞭解你
And I sent you to St. Louis  so he could spend time with you,
給我他的建議
give me his 2 cents.
恕我直問，什麼建議？
On what, sir, if I may ask?
讓你當副總統
Offering you the Vice Presidency.
我告訴了總統
I told the President that,
就我個人的小小看法
in my humble opinion,
如果有像你這樣經驗豐富
both he and the country  would be well-served
明智和忠誠的人當副總統
by a man as experienced,
他和國家都會受益
intelligent, and loyal as you.
因此我正式問你，法蘭
So I'm officially asking, Frank.
總統，我不知道要說什麼
Sir, l... I don't know what to say.
就說好
Say yes.
好
Yes.
這是莫大的榮幸，總統先生
It would be a great honor, Mr. President.
米契
Meechum.
我照顧自己的人
I take care of my own,
你也證明了自己很有價值
and you've proved yourself  to be very valuable.
等我確認後，我要你加入
I would like you to be  part of my security detail
我的保安特遣隊
once I get confirmed.
那是特勤隊，先生  我是國會警察
That's the Secret Service, sir.  I'm Capitol Police.
那麼我會把你調到特勤隊
Then I'll put you on the Secret Service.
只要你有興趣
If you're interested.
我非常有興趣，先生
I'd be more than interested, sir.
很好
Good.
我也很感激
And I'm extremely grateful.
繼續發揮價值
Keep being valuable.
那就是你展現感激的最好方式
That's the best way to show your gratitude.
我會的
I will.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President.
水電工終於來了
Did the plumber finally come?
不，是我修的
No. I fixed it.
法蘭斯
Francis.
真替你驕傲，法蘭斯
So proud of you, Francis.
我不是靠自己做到的
But I didn't do it alone.
我盡快趕來了
I got here as quickly as I could.
出了什麼事嗎？
Is something wrong?
我要你完全誠實對我說  克裏絲汀娜
I need you to be completely  honest with me, Christina.
說什麼？
About what?
前幾天  我說若有媒體糾纏你
The other day, when I said  that you should tell me
你該告訴我？
if anyone from the press  started harassing you?
喬伊邦斯？
Zoe Barnes?
你在電話上說你有事要談
You said you wanted to talk  about something on the phone.
那不急
Oh, no. That can wait.
來吧，告訴我
No. Come on. Tell me.
我…今天稍早時…
I... Earlier today...
我看到划船機壞了
The rowing machine, I saw, is broken.
那是我的錯，線斷了
Oh, it's my fault. The cable broke.
我還沒時間更換
I haven't been able to replace it yet.
跟我去跑步如何？
What about going for a run with me?
她想譭謗安德沃議員
She's trying to smear  Congressman Underwood.
那是《頭條報導》的聯合活動
It's a coordinated campaign  by everyone at Slugline.
但她知道事情
But she knew things.
- 比如什麼？  - 彼得的事
-Like what?  -About Peter.
跟凱恩失去提名有關
Something to do with Kern  losing the nomination.
還有呢？
And?
要我開車跟著你嗎，議員？
Want me to drive alongside you, sir?
不，你留在這裏
No. You stay here.
好的，議員
Yes, sir.
準備好沒？
You ready?
好了
Yes.
道格史坦普